[
  {
      "title": "Children’s TV Trivia"
  },

  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is the name of the red furry monster on Sesame Street?",
    "answer": "Elmo."
},
  {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "What is the name of the animated bear who lived in a cottage with Aunt Lucy?",
      "answer": "Paddington Bear."
  },
  {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "In 'Teletubbies,' what is the name of the vacuum cleaner?",
      "answer": "Noo-Noo."
  },
  {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which TV show features Squirrel Club?",
      "answer": "Hey Duggee."
  },
  {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "What was the name of the show where children completed art challenges with Neil Buchanan?",
      "answer": "Art Attack."
  },
  {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which children's TV show features a group of animated puppies who work together on rescue missions in Adventure Bay?",
      "answer": "Paw Patrol."
  },
  {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "In which animated series do siblings George, Harold, and their principal-turned-superhero embark on comedic adventures?",
      "answer": "The Epic Tales of Captain Underpants."
  },
  {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Which children's show features a young girl who goes on adventures with her monkey friend Boots, often involving map-reading and problem-solving?",
      "answer": "Dora the Explorer."
  },
  {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "What is the name of Peppa Pig’s little brother?",
      "answer": "George."
  },
  {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "What breed of dog is Bluey?",
      "answer": "Blue Heeler."
  }
]